gdstarrating.com 2016-03-16

# GD Star Rating | Privacy Policy »

Posted by MillaN | January 7, 2009, 12:18 AM 

**What information do we collect?**  
 **** We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.gdstarrating.com/

milan@gdragon.info

**GD Star Rating**  
 _a WordPress rating system_
